<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Safety on German Driving Prep</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/safety/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Safety on German Driving Prep</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/safety/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Patience and Calmness Protocol</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/patience-and-calmness-protocol/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/patience-and-calmness-protocol/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the most important file. Read it last. This is a test of safety, &lt;strong&gt;not a race&lt;/strong&gt;. Rushing leads to mistakes. Patience demonstrates control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;if-you-are-behind-a-cyclist&#34;&gt;If You Are Behind a Cyclist&amp;hellip;
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Action:&lt;/strong&gt; You wait. Maintain a safe distance. You only overtake when you can guarantee the minimum &lt;strong&gt;1.5-meter&lt;/strong&gt; side distance and the road ahead is completely clear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Reality:&lt;/strong&gt; Waiting behind a cyclist for 30 seconds is &lt;strong&gt;correct driving&lt;/strong&gt;. A rushed, unsafe overtake is a &lt;strong&gt;fail&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;if-you-need-to-yield-for-a-clear-space-&#34;&gt;If You Need to Yield for a Clear Space (e.g., at a Yield sign)&amp;hellip;
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Action:&lt;/strong&gt; You wait. You wait until a gap appears that is large enough for you to enter &lt;strong&gt;safely and without forcing&lt;/strong&gt; the other cars to brake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Reality:&lt;/strong&gt; Taking an extra 10 seconds to correctly judge a safe gap is &lt;strong&gt;good driving&lt;/strong&gt;. Pulling out into a small gap and causing another car to slow down is an &lt;strong&gt;endangerment&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;fail&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;if-you-are-waiting-to-turn-left-and-causing-a-traffic-jam&#34;&gt;If You Are Waiting to Turn Left and Causing a Traffic Jam&amp;hellip;
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Action:&lt;/strong&gt; You wait. Oncoming traffic has &lt;strong&gt;absolute priority&lt;/strong&gt;. Your only job is to wait in your position until there is a safe gap for you to turn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Reality:&lt;/strong&gt; Waiting for one minute while cars pile up behind you is &lt;strong&gt;100% correct driving&lt;/strong&gt;. The traffic behind you is legally required to wait for you. Turning in front of oncoming traffic is the &lt;strong&gt;most dangerous mistake&lt;/strong&gt; you can make and an &lt;strong&gt;instant, absolute fail&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-final-mantra&#34;&gt;Your Final Mantra
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The cars behind me do not matter. The clock does not matter. Only the space in front of me and the rules matter.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are not being judged on your speed. You are being judged on your safety. By being patient, you are demonstrating that you are a safe driver. You are correct. Be calm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
